

# Mostakimul Karim

# Full Stack Web Developer



+39 3290855636



linkedin.com/mostakimul



mostakimulkarim@gmail.com



github.com/Mostakimul

# CAREER OBJECTIVE

Effective and determined full stack developer with efficient problem solving skills and analytical capabilities. Always look forward to the new challenges. Worked as a freelance developer in various online markets and improved skills as an efficient developer. Worked on 20+ different projects using various technologies.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# APRIL, 2021 - PRESENT

AAK TELE-SCIENCE, INC.

#### **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

 Working remotely for developing website which is under development process.

### **2020 - PRESENT**

Upwork

# **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

 Developed an agency website for online presence and giving quote to the users as their requirements with 100% client satisfaction.

# MAY, 2020 -APRIL, 2021

**Fiverr** (Level 1 Seller)

# **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

- Guided over 10 clients for implementation for their websites.
- Boosted client website for fast loading speed.
- Worked on SEO for better search result.
- Built Wordpress Website for a learning system using Learndash.

#### **EDUCATION**

# 2017 - PRESENT

#### UNITED INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Computer Science & Engineering

CGPA: 3.18( current)

2016 GOVT. SCIENCE COLLEGE

**Science** GPA: 4.75 out of 5.00

2014 CHATKHIL P.G GOVT. HIGH SCHOOL

**Science** GPA: 5.00 out of 5.00

# **SKILLS WEB DEVELOPMENT** LARAVEL HTML MYSQLI CSS **WORDPRESS BOOTSTRAP** TAILWIND CSS AJAX **JQUERY** SAAS **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES JAVASCRIPT** С PHP JAVA **PYTHON** SOFTWARE VSCODE ADOBE **PHOTOSHOP SUBLIME** ADOBE MOTA **ILLUSTRATOR MICROSOFT VEGAS PRO OFFICE** SOFT SKILLS **DILIGENT** FAST LEARNER • • **AMIABLE EFFICIENT COMPOSURE**

#### CERTIFICATION

- RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN CodersTrust Bangladesh
- FRONT-END WEB UI FRAMEWORKS AND **TOOLS: BOOTSTRAP 4**

Coursera

# WEB DEVELOPMENT

Creative IT Institute

• HTML5, CSS3 & **BOOTSTRAP 4 FOR WEB DEVELOPMENT** 

Bohubrihi

# **OTHERS EXPERIENCE**

### **2020 - PRESENT**

### **CAMPUSS AMBASSADOR**

Myth Musuem

- · Promoting the necessity of IT skills.
- · Organizing events to help students for understanding the new technologies.

#### **2019 - PRESENT TREASURER**

**UIU SPORTS CLUB** 

2018 - 2019 **CAMPUSS AMBASSADOR** 

**Creative IT** 

**2020 - PRESENT HEAD OF MEDIA, PUBLISHER & IT** 

**UIU Theatre & Film** Club

# **REFERENCES**

#### TARIQUE HASAN

**Software Engineer** Creative IT Institute

#### TARIQ MANON

Web Mentor & Career Advisor CodersTrust Bangladesh 

